Illuru, Illuru, were you playing with those humans again?
I love humans very much, they're so nice!
I see. Then perhaps it is time we consider coexisting with these mortal beings.
Bad news! The humans are attacking the Dragon Village!
This always happens when we choose to stay silent.
Damn humans, they will pay!
Weird's mommy and daddy!
I'm sorry, my dear.
Does this mean I can't play with the humans anymore?
Of course it does! Those humans are the ones who took your parents away from you!
They will forever be our enemy. We will never come to an understanding.
Oh, good. Everyone's asleep.
Seeing one of those up close for the first time is traumatic enough without it being mine.
Hey! There you are, Miss Kobayashi! Welcome home!
Will you please let me know next time you're going to be late?
Oh, yeah. I'm sorry.
Your face is flushed and sweaty. Are you feeling okay?
Huh?
Maybe you're catching a cold.
Yes! Don't touch me! I'm fine!
What the hell? Why do I start to sweat and almost pass out whenever I look at her?
Is it lust? Am I lusting now? After Toru?
Go put your clothes on, please.
Okay.
Kobayashi, you can't hide anymore now that you're a man.
You'll show everyone your true colors in no time.
But I get to see first. Show me how shallow humans are.
That's totally what this is about.
I bet Alulu turned me into a dude so that I would unwittingly display the worst of humanity.
I just hope it's over soon.
Although, I have no idea what she's trying to get out of me.
I definitely need to keep a clear head as a dude.
Hmm.
Hey! What are you doing here?
I'm snuggling. Good morning.
But why?
I was worried you'd be cold this morning.
Okay! I'm warm! I'm warm and awake!
Time to start the day!
I have no idea how this thing works or when it might activate.
Which is why I'll need to keep my distance from the others.
I wonder if this is something Toru could fix.
What? This Kobayashi's a man?
What are we waiting for?
Let's work on preserving our species!
Maybe I'll wait.
Okay, it's time to ride the canoe to adventure.
What are you watching, Kana?
It's called clinky-clang.
Is everybody ready?
Let's go!
Go!
Now let's get paddling!
Oh, no!
There's a waterfall up ahead!
Total disregard for personal space
is normal between female friends.
It's what we do.
I can handle it.
I will not allow this penis to define my instincts.
Save me!
Do not hug me for no reason!
Kobayashi!
Get up!
Please get up!
Ms. Kobayashi!
What did I tell you about random hug attacks?
Hi!
Get out!
That was so close.
I've forgotten how clingy she is.
Thank goodness.
It's finally gone smaller.
I figured Elulu's powers had been weakened during her battle with Toru.
Trying to remember the factions from Toru's world.
Elulu's from the Chaos Faction, too, I think.
They hate humans, and they raise their children with the same principles.
Elulu grew up that way.
It's the only truth she knows.
She can't help the way she thinks.
Good evening, Ms. Kobayashi.
Huh?
Kana's already asleep.
What do you say?
How about a nightcap?
Good stuff.
Yep.
That's it.
I'm done overthinking my anatomy today.
What the?
I recognize this feeling.
The love potion?
You thought I wouldn't notice it, didn't you?
Oh, I know your scent very well.
You have fully parts!
This is Elulu's work, isn't it?
I'm sorry, Ms. Kobayashi.
I'll get you back to normal soon.
But not just yet.
I'm not going to throw away this opportunity.
Our hearts have become intimate.
Now we get out our bodies.
Come on, Ms. Kobayashi.
I'm ready to receive you now.
Wait, are you completely turned off?
Where's your maid outfit?
You took it off?
Toru, I'm going to tell you why maids are great,
but with my man-brain.
Finally.
Now that that's over,
what will you try to do next, Elulu?
Very good job.
It's displayed nicely, Miss.
Hmm.
Something's still not right about it.
There we go.
So wonderful.
Slow down.
Stop running.
You followed me here, you harmony bastard!
I am Kremina, a dragon slayer.
Please give my name to the judge in the underworld after you die.
I want all the credit.
Where is she?
Elulu always seems to appear when I'm alone after work.
Maybe she'll show up if I wait here.
But why would I do that?
I might be focusing on Elulu a little too much.
I wonder if it's because I feel like we could get along somehow.
All the dragons I've met from other worlds have been friendly,
so it makes sense.
They all have this air of having survived conflict with humans,
ending in tragic results.
Yet they remain tolerant of people in general.
They understand we're not all like that.
They're willing to believe there's more to us than the trouble we cause.
And that's how I feel about Toru too.
Which is why it's important for her to reconcile with Elulu.
Keep the peace.
Of course she's not showing up.
Maybe she went over here where there's less foot traffic.
Elulu!
Are you injured?
You've seen us, have you?
Greetings, human of this world.
I've come here to destroy that vile beast before you from the Chaos Faction.
You must leave this place immediately and forget everything you witnessed here tonight.
Who is this jerk?
You came all the way here to kill Elulu?
So you're a grown adult here trying to kill a child?
I am.
That creature is pure chaos.
An evil dragon that will bring harm to humans.
Well, if that's the case, then...
Huh?
Ah!
Oh.
That is a most unpleasant sound.
Hey!
Keep it down out there!
All right!
Security buzzer power!
How much do you weigh?
It seems they've escaped.
What's that human thinking?
Hi.
Can you see my face?
How are you feeling?
It looks like your wound healed up freakishly fast, at least.
Why did you save me?
Hard to tell if the coast is clear.
I bet that creeper's still after you, huh?
I don't know.
Hmm?
I shouldn't avoid battles.
If I die, that means it was my fate.
Well, if that's the case, then me wanting to save you would also be your fate.
Hey, Elulu?
Is there something else you want to tell me?
You seem to have this constant toot, and it's making me a little concerned.
I told you, I can't accept dragons coexisting with humans.
It's not possible for them to ever get along.
Oh, yeah.
I remember that, kinda.
Because if they can get along, then that means...
That means I wasted so many years believing the lies!
Dragons are superior, so to associate with humans is shameful.
I just...
They caused all kinds of tragedies.
Harmony is now impossible.
But I...
Humans are our enemy.
It's not fair.
I just went...
So badly!
One more time!
Please, just let me fight with them again!
But they wouldn't let me.
That girl and that boy did nothing bad to us, and yet...
I'm so sorry.
Don't listen.
Why don't we all play together next time?
We do all kinds of things you might like.
We play dodgeball, go to kamiket, go to hot springs, lots of stuff.
But...
You'll have to chill out on the kind of play that turns into battles.
You...
You're trying to trick me!
You're saying all these nice things to me to try and win me over!
Yeah, I guess I am.
You caught me trying to tame a fierce, evil chaos dragon with kindness and friendship so that I might render her harmless.
You can still believe what you've been taught.
Or would you like to be tricked by me?
I would...
That's enough.
I can't believe you and that human were working together.
I'll exterminate you both.
Can you do that?
Don't you have rules, too?
Those rules only exist on paper.
And they only apply to dragons.
So if you think it's safe for you to corrupt our species, try it.
This guy's making Toru's father seem like a baby garden gecko.
But...
Humans can be so much worse.
A human who's trying to protect a dragon?
Kobayashi!
Ow!
Okay, that would hurt for real.
Well, look who's late.
Impossible.
How did you get here?
You dare hurt Miss Kobayashi!
I'm not threatened by you.
I have reinforcements waiting to be summoned.
Lady Emma will be here to...
Choose your words wisely, you coward.
Maybe if you beg, I'll let you keep your soul after I crush you.
Go ahead.
Beg for your worthless life.
Ah!
Um, did I witness murder?
No, I just erased his memories of this world and then sent him back from whence he came.
Um, but not before I punished him, of course.
Of course.
Thank goodness.
Now a Lulu can chill.
Oh, gross.
Now that we're okay, I'm feeling...
Ah!
Miss Kobayashi!
Don't worry, I'll help you out.
Drugs and Slime can stop bleeding instantly by just making up excuses to liquor!
Are you ready, Miss Kobayashi?
Lick-lick-lick-lick-lick-lick-lick-lick-lick-lick-lick-lick-lick-lick-lick-lick-lick-lick.
Your tongue is obscene, what you are.
And that's when I met Toru.
And when she managed to change me for the better.
I wonder if maybe I was seeing my old self in Ilulu.
Miss Kobayashi?
You're finally awake!
Everything will be alright.
Toru?
Hey there, Kana.
Are we in our home?
We are.
I brought you back here and healed your wounds, too.
Where did Ilulu go?
She's right there.
I tried to send her off, but she wouldn't leave your side.
I'm glad she finally sees what we figured out ages ago, but it's just a little too late.
Kobayashi!
Will you please trick me?
Sure.
I'd love to.
Good morning.
El Niño Miki is here to bring you today's national weather.
What do we do about that tail?
I guess those claws don't retract.
Is it possible to make her chest more family-friendly?
I mean, come on.
Believe it or not, Ilulu is already pushing herself to maintain a modest size.
If she wasn't, I'm not so sure she'd be able to fit through the door.
Oh, I bet she could hide her claws and tail somewhere if she tried.
Wait!
Since when can't she control body parts?
All I need is about 5% of that.
Kobayashi!
Hey, what's up?
This is where we eliminate waste, right?
How does it work?
Uh, we're doing this?
Yep.
Hop on up there.
And that's basically it.
I got it.
I guess we'll have to teach her all kinds of things.
If only I had a talented maid to help me in times like these.
I'd probably see them in a whole new light.
I'm sorry about this.
I promise it'll just be while I'm at work.
Don't be silly, it's fine.
It's what you do for someone when you have a special eternal bond with them.
I'm not feeling ready to use the word eternal.
Okay, bye!
Have you been pumped with those muscles, Dad?
When you stop working out, these stuff's crazy.
It's weird.
We were trying to kill each other just days ago.
There's no way Toru would ever forgive a traitor.
I know she's planning to eliminate me.
But I want to spend more time with Kobayashi.
And I'm not going down without a fight.
There's no fighting.
Here.
This is the manual I wrote about how to live your life as a human.
Rule number A, change your claws into hands.
How is it funny to fail at the one task you're given?
Do you suck at everything or just making hands?
I can't transform them well.
But I can still read.
At least you can hold some stuff with those things.
It's a ball of tiny hands, look!
Ew!
Gross!
Greetings.
Humans establish communication with greetings.
For now, just repeat whatever greeting one says to you.
Food.
Humans will mostly eat anything.
But they stubbornly won't eat dragon meat.
Currently seeking ways to get them to change this.
Mating.
I want to do it.
Everything in here is biased!
It is the whole truth and nothing but.
Clothing.
Wearing clothing similar to what other humans wear will keep you from standing out.
Doesn't look like you're trying to blend in.
What?
Bud, whatever you say.
I can wear human clothes if we're supposed to.
We don't have your size here.
What about Kana's stuff?
She's even smaller!
Look!
It fits!
See, what did I tell you?
Quit making things complicated and transform your scales the way I do.
I don't have the skills to do it, okay?
Sad for you.
But I can lend you something of mine.
So, what do you plan to contribute here?
I haven't thought about it.
Well, what are you good at?
There has to be something, right?
Yeah, I'm sure there is.
I'm thinking.
Are you, though?
Mm-hmm.
Well, you are welcome to stay in our home as long as you would like until you make a decision.
Can you say it without twitching?
I know this may come as a surprise to you, Mushroom Mitz, but I'm not particularly thrilled to have you here as a house guest.
Not surprised at all.
Think about that humiliating grand entrance you made.
We thought you were some crazy, bloodthirsty berserker.
Whatever.
I was bored and fighting you seemed like fun.
Are you trying to say that's what I look like?
All I know is you better figure out what you want your job to be.
There's a saying that goes, those who don't work don't eat.
What about Kana?
Kana can't work.
She's an elementary school student.
Okay, then fine.
I'll be an elementary school student, too.
You have to be a child to go to school, dummy.
And I'm guessing you're about the same age as me, aren't you?
Maybe.
Hurry up and make a choice.
I'm back!
Welcome home!
What's going on with you, Lulu?
She's thinking about how she wants to contribute around here.
Hmm.
Whatever you choose will be great.
What's wrong?
I figured out what I want to do while I'm here.
Okay, cool.
What is it?
I want to make babies with you.
Huh?
You see, I thought about it and I'm at the perfect age to reproduce and raise healthy children.
I'm very lonely from not having a family and I think you're the one to rescue me.
Kobayashi, I want you to mate with me.
You want it?
I don't know what you're trying to pull, ma'am, but you've crossed over the light and back!
Also, we're both female.
I can give your thing back.
Don't you dare unless you want her to use it on me!
Pervert.
Yep.
I mean it!
I'm not trying to hold on to my purity, but I'm also not trying to get with dragons.
Surprise!
I thought you might like it.
Ahaha!
Bye!
Where are you going to sleep, you Lulu?
We don't have space for another bed.
What about in here?
The closet?
It's calming.
I mean, if you're okay with it, sure.
Yeah, I like it.
This week on Who's Rotten?
Cancer!